Hi, welcome to session 10,
嗨，欢迎来到第十节课，
in this session, we're gonna cover arpeggios,
在这节课中，我们将讨论琶音，
finger picking, a little bit about fingerstyle technique,
指弹，指弹技巧，
what's good hand technique for finger picking,
什么是好的指弹技巧，
I'm going to give you some simple finger patterns,
我会给你们一些简单的手指模式，
as well we're going to talk about Merle Travis style guitar,
我们还会讨论 Merle Travis 风格的吉他，
a very popular a country style,
一种非常流行的乡村风格，
I'm sure you'll recognize it once we start,
我相信一旦我们开始，你们就会认出它，
getting into it,
认识它，
we're going to talk a little bit about classical guitar
我们将讨论一些古典吉他，
and the techniques that you use for that,
和你使用的技巧，
in the guitar tips section,
在吉他 tips 一节中，
we're gonna cover how to get control of your playing
我们将讨论如何控制你的演奏速度，
speed versus control,
速度与控制，
the only way you can get speed is through control,
你获得速度的唯一方法是通过控制，
so we're going to talk about that,
所以我们要谈到这一点，
so I hope you're ready,
所以我希望你准备好了，
let's go and started.
我们开始吧。
Okay, let's talk about finger style guitar and finger picking,
好的，让我们来谈谈指弹，
we use arpeggios,
我们用琶音，
which is a new term for you, new concept for you,
这是一个新的术语，对你们来说，
all in arpeggio is,
琶音是，
we've done our chords, D chord,
我们已经做好了和弦， D 和弦，
let's say I'm doing a G chord,
假设我在弹奏 G 和弦，
okay, all arpeggio is,
好的，所有的琶音就是，
I take notes of those chords instead of playing altogether,
我弹下那些和弦音符，而不是一起演奏，
I play I break them up,
我把它们分开，
it was a G chord like this,
它是一个像这样的 G 和弦，
so when I set it gone,
所以当我弹奏的时候，
that are using arpeggios, something like,
使用琶音，像这样，
okay, that was arpeggio is.
好的，这就是琶音。
Now, in order to get good fingerstyle technique,
现在，为了获得好的指弹技巧，
there's a couple things we need to always keep in mind.
有几件事我们需要始终牢记。
And it all starts with some very key right-hand concepts,
这一切都是从一些非常关键的右手概念开始的，
we're going to be mainly dealing with this hand, for this session today,
在今天的课程中，我们将主要讨论这只手，
so here's how you can start to have a good right hand position,
所以这是如何开始你的右手位置的，
when you're starting fingerstyle stuff.
当你开始指弹风格的东西时。
The first thing you need to have is a very relaxed hand.
你首先需要的是一只非常放松的手。
Okay, so how are we gonna do that,
好的，我们该怎么做呢，
I want you just take your hand,
我想让你抓起你的手，
take your arm put it down to your side,
把你的胳膊放在身体的一侧，
just completely relax it,
完全放松它，
your hand normally comes to this kind of C looking shape,
你的手通常会变成这种看起来像 C 的形状，
okay,
好的，
and with that shape,
有了这样的形状，
just like that just kind of bring that up to your guitar,
就可以把它带到你的吉他上，
this is actually, let's say it's the zero point of your muscles,
这是，比如说你的肌肉的零点，
there's two kinds of muscles that run in your hand,
有两种肌肉在你的手上，
actually three kinds,
实际上有三种，
but there's the two that we're going to talk about today,
但我们今天要讨论的是两种，
the ones that run on top, when I flex those,
一个是上面的，当我弯曲它们时，
my finger goes up,
我的手指竖起，
when I flex the ones that run underneath,
当我弯曲手指下面的，
my finger goes in,
我的手指向内，
so actually the zero position is this rather C looking form right here,
所以零位置是这个看起来像 C 的形式，
that's where you want to start at,
这就是你想要开始的地方，
you don't want to start at an uncomfortable stressful position
你不想从一个不舒服的有压力的位置开始，
or you'll never get the concepts that we're going to talk about,
否则你永远不会得到我们将要讨论的概念，
so take that relaxed hand,
所以拿出那只放松的手，
go ahead, put it up to your strings
继续，把它放在你的琴弦上，
and I've got to just kind of adjust it a little bit to get, to get it on the strings,
我必须稍微调整一下才能放到琴弦上，
okay, I'm gonna put my thumb,
好的，我要把我的拇指放在，
just for our purposes right now,
为了我们的目标，
I'm gonna put my thumb on the sixth string,
我要把我的拇指放在第六根弦上，
just gonna set it right there,
把它放在那里，
I'm gonna put my first finger on the third string,
我要把我的食指放在第三根弦上，
I'm going to put my second finger on that second string,
把我的中指放在第二根弦上，
and the third finger on that first string.
还有无名指在第一根弦上。
Got it,
明白了吗，
so we're dealing with the six string the third string, the second string and the first string,
所以我们处理第六根弦，第三根弦，第二根弦和第一根弦，
now as I fire my fingers,
现在当我击发我的手指，
think of your fingers firing like a piston,
想像你的手指像活塞一样击发，
as each one goes goes through its movements,
因为每一个都有它的移动，
you want to have freedom of motion,
你想要有运动的自由，
now look what I had to do,
看看我必须做的，
I have to kind of bring my thumb forward just slightly
我必须稍微把我的拇指向前，
and my wrist out,
把我的手腕伸出来，
if you don't want your wrist back in there like this,
如果你不想让你的手腕像这样回到那里，
you don't want to be like that,
你不会想要这样，
you may be tempted to do that,
你可能会忍不住这样做，
because you think you kind of need all that pressure to do that,
因为你认为你需要这样做，
actually the best thing to do bring that wrist out,
实际上最好的做法是把手腕伸出来，
and that thumb forward slightly,
拇指稍微向前一点，
doesn't need to be way out of here out of [],
不需要偏离这里，
just forward a little bit slightly.
只需要稍微向前一点。
Okay, and now we're going to fire all four of these,
好了，现在我们要拨动所有四个，
okay, so the thumb goes and then first finger, second finger, third finger.
好的，所以拇指，然后是食指，中指，无名指。
Let's do that one more time,
让我们再来一次，
thumb, first, second, third,
拇指，食指，中指，无名指，
for our purposes,
出于我们的目的，
we're going to name these,
我们将给它们命名，
in your, in your book, they're going to be referenced as,
在你的书中，它们将被指定为，
thumb will be T, first will be 1, second will be 2, third will be 3,
拇指是 T ，食指是 1 ，中指是 2 ，无名指是 3 ，
in classical guitar technique,
在古典吉他技巧中，
they call them different, different things,
他们称它们为不同的东西，
thumb would be P,
拇指是 P ，
sometimes you'll see P I M A,
有时你会看到 P I M A ，
I, index would be first finger,
I, index 是食指，
M, middle
M, middle 是中指，
and then A would be your third finger,
然后 A 是你的无名指，
okay, but for our purposes,
但是对于我们的目标，
we're just going to have thumb 1 2 3, T 1 2 and 3.
我们只有拇指 1 2 3 ， T 1 2 3 。
Okay, here's the first finger pattern that you need to work on,
好的，这是你需要练习的第一个手指模式，
it starts on the open strings,
它是从空弦开始的，
we're going to put our hand right up here,
我们要把你的手放在这里，
move that thumb forward just a little bit slightly,
把拇指稍微向前移动一点，
you don't want him to hit that first finger,
你不会想让它碰到食指，
we're going to go through this real slowly,
我们会非常缓慢地进行这个过程，
this is going to sound dumb,
这听起来很愚蠢，
if anybody's listening over your shoulder in the room that you're listening to,
如果房间里有人在你身后听这个，
this is not going to make much sense to them,
这对他们来说没有多大意义，
it's just gonna sound like we're making noise,
听起来就像我们在制造噪音，
but don't worry about that,
但不要担心，
we're trying to get these finger concepts, okay.
我们努力理解这些手指概念，好吗？
Here we go,
我们开始，
so we'll do it nice and slow,
所以我们要慢慢地做，
this is finger exercise one.
这是手指练习一。
Open string, open string, open string, open string,
空弦，空弦，空弦，空弦，
thumb 1 2 3,
拇指 1 2 3 ，
okay, we don't use our pinky
好的，我们不用我们的小指，
and the secret to all of this is go slow,
所有这些的秘诀就是慢下来，
I know you're tempted to go real fast
我知道你很想快点，
and get get to plan all the faster stuff,
开始计划所有更快的事情，
you'll never get fast, unless it's in control,
你永远不会快，除非它在控制中，
control is the key for speed,
控制是速度的关键，
you want to go for control, not for speed,
你想要的是控制，而不是速度，
once I get you control
一旦你能控制，
and your hand doing what your brain is telling it to do,
你的手做你的大脑告诉它的事情，
then you'll get as fast as you can go,
你就会得到尽可能快的速度，
but I can't get you just start playing fast,
但你开始弹奏很快，
you'll forever be tripping over yourself
你会永远被自己绊倒，
and trying to get this [flow] right.
试图获得这种流动。
Okay, let's try one more time.
好的，让我们再试一次。
Ready, a bit faster,
准备，稍微快一点，
thumb 1 2 3,
拇指， 1 2 3 ，
all of your fingers should be coming up into your hand.
你所有的手指都应该伸到你的手中。
Now let's add some chords with it,
现在让我们添加一些和弦，
let's start on exercise 2 with a G chord,
让我们开始练习二， G 和弦，
just regular open g,
常规的开放的 G ，
same fingers on the same strings.
同样的手指在同样的琴弦上。
Let's go,
我们开始，
T, thumb 1 2 3,
T ，拇指 1 2 3 ，
I know it's a lot to keep track of as we just get started,
我知道开始的时候很难掌握，
but as you do it more and more,
但随着你做得越来越多，
you'll eventually start running on autopilot
你会开始自动驾驶，
and you don't have to think about it,
你不需要想它，
near as much as you're having to right now.
就像你现在必须做的那样。
Let's go to a C chord,
让我们转到 C 和弦，
now my thumb is going to switch to the fifth string,
现在我的拇指将切换到第五根弦，
these bottom three fingers still stay on the bottom three strings,
下面的三个手指仍然停留在下面的三根弦上，
ready, play,,
准备，演奏，
thumb 1 2 3,
拇指 1 2 3 ，
thumb 1 2 3.
拇指 1 2 3 。
Now I'll switch to a D chord,
现在我要切换到 D 和弦，
now my thumb is going to switch down,
现在我的拇指要向下切换，
he's on the fourth string now,
它在第四根弦上，
thumb 1 2 3,
拇指 1 2 3 ，
each finger is firing up into that hand at the right time,
每个手指在正确的时间弹奏，
fine motor skill controls, what we're developing here.
我们在研究精细的运动技能控制。
Okay, we're now switching between two chords,
好的，现在我们在两个和弦之间切换，
we're going to switch between a G and a C chord,
我们将在 G 和 C 和弦之间切换，
okay, we'll do four measures with G, four measures with C,
好的，我们弹四小节的 G ，四小节的 C ，
now you're jumping from the fifth string or the sixth string with your thumb
现在你的拇指从第五根弦或第六根弦
to the fifth string with your thumb.
跳到第五根弦。
Okay, a little bit faster now,
好的，现在再快一点，
that we've had a chance to work on it.
我们有机会去做了。
Ready, go,
准备，开始，
G chord,
G 和弦，
C chord, fifth string on that C,
C 和弦，第五根弦，
here you go,
干得不错，
keep that thumb front, good.
保持拇指在前面，很好。
Okay, let's go to the next one,
好的，让我们进入下一个，
now we're gonna switch between D and G and D and A,
现在我们要在 D 和 G ， D 和 A 之间切换，
okay, we're speeding it up a little bit more.
好的，我们把速度再提高一点。
Ready go,
准备，开始，
thumb 1 2 3,
拇指 1 2 3 ，
G chord,
G 和弦，
back to D,
回到 D ，
A chord.
A 和弦。
Very good,
非常好，
okay, that was our first fingerstyle pattern right there,
好的，这是我们的第一个指弹模式，
thumb 1 2 3,
拇指 1 2 3 ，
now we're going to just invert that a little bit,
现在我们要把它倒过来，
so it's going to be thumb 3 2 1,
所以它将是拇指 3 2 1 ，
you try that, thumb 3 2 1,
你试一下，拇指 3 2 1 ，
everybody thinks they know how to move their fingers
每个人都认为他们知道如何移动手指，
until we start asking them to do a find things like this
直到我们开始要求他们做这样的事情，
and then you realize how how little you actually move your fingers this way,
然后你意识到你很少这样移动你的手指，
here we go on a G chord, thumb 3 2 1,
我们开始， G 和弦，拇指 3 2 1 ，
ready, go,,
准备，开始，
go to a C chord,, right.
换到 C 和弦。
Okay, let's go to exercise number 2 starts with a D chord,
好的，让我们来做练习 2 ，从 D 和弦开始，
we'll go a little bit faster now.
我们现在会快一点。
Ready go,
准备，开始，
now you're finding I'm going too fast for you,
你发现我的速度对你来说太快了，
you may just want to press pause for a second,
你可能想按下暂停一下，
and work on these skills for a second,
练习一下这些技巧，
to get them up to the speed that we need to get them at,
让它们达到我们需要的速度，
go ahead and continue on,
继续并前进，
as if we have gotten up to speed on these next ones.
如果我们已经跟上了下一个的速度。
Okay, now we've covered finger exercise 1, thumb 1 2 3,
好的，现在我们已经涵盖了手指练习 1 ，拇指 1 2 3 ，
finger pattern number 2, thumb 3 2 1,
手指模式 2 ，拇指 3 2 1 ，
and the last one that I use is thumb 2 1 3,
我用的最后一个是，拇指 2 1 3 ，
thumb 2 1 3.
拇指 2 1 3 。
Let's try that one,
我们试试那个，
exercise number 3, starts with a G.
练习三，从 G 开始。
Let's try that one, a little bit slow,
让我们试试那个，慢一点，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
thumb 2 1 3,
拇指 2 1 3 ，
thumb 2 1,
拇指 2 1 ，
now, to C.
现在，切换到 C 。
Very good.
非常好。
Okay, now as you speed that up,
好的，现在随着你加速，
it starts to sound a little bit more like music,
它开始听起来有点像音乐，
let's say, I'm going from a D chord to maybe an A chord,
比如，我从 D 和弦切换到 A 和弦，
thumb 2 1 3, thumb 2 1 3, thumb 2 1 3, thumb 2 1 3,,
拇指 2 1 3 ，拇指 2 1 3 ，拇指 2 1 3 ，拇指 2 1 3 ，
now, you get faster,
现在你变得更快，
you're gonna want to clamp that hand down,
你会想要压下你的手，
bring that wrist flat,
把手腕平放，
wrong thing to do,
这样做是错误的，
you have to be controlled and relaxed in your wrist.
你的手腕必须控制和放松。
Next thing we're going to talk about is finger picking with a pick.
接下来我们要讨论的是用拨片的指弹。
Okay, now just for a brief second,
好的，现在我们简短的，
we're going to talk about finger picking with a pick,
讨论一下用拨片的指弹，
which is something you do a lot,
这是你经常做的事情，
is if you're strumming a little bit,
如果你弹一点，
then you want to do some fingerstyle stuff with it.
那么你就想用它来做一些指弹的东西。
You put your pick of course between your thumb and your first finger like normal,
你可以像往常一样把拨片放在拇指和食指之间，
now that unit just kind of starts to act as one,
现在这个单元就像一个整体，
so you can still use two and three to do the picking that you need to do,
所以你仍然可以用 2 和 3 来做你需要的拨动，
so if I'm going in a D chord,
所以如果我在 D 和弦，
I do my thumb and first, which are now as work as one.
我的拇指和食指，现在是个整体。
Let's say, I want to do thumb 2 1 3,
假设我想做拇指 2 1 3 ，
which doesn't land as well,
没有像之前一样，
it would then the thumb would have to cover both spots,
那么拇指必须覆盖两个点，
thumb 2, thumb 3,
拇指 2 ，拇指 3 ，
see what I did there,
看我做了什么，
thumb 2, thumb 3, thumb 2, thumb 3,
拇指 2 ，拇指 3 ，拇指 2 ，拇指 3 ，
he's just pulling double duty now,
它现在做双重任务，
that we're using a pick,
因为我们用了拨片，
thumb 2 1 3, thumb 2 thumb 3, sorry.
拇指 2 1 3 ，拇指 2 拇指 3 ，抱歉。
So you can do fingerstyle stuff with your pick,
所以你能用你的拨片做指弹的东西，
you just need to figure out how you're going to do that,
你只需要弄清楚如何做，
in a little bit of practice with it.
用它做一些练习。
Okay, now we're going to talk about the Merle Travis style of picking,
好的，现在我们要谈谈 Merle Travis 的拨片风格，
Merle Travis was a great country guitar player,
Merle Travis 是一个伟大的乡村吉他手，
for many years gone by,
很多年前，
but he really developed this whole style of picking,
但他发展了整个拨片风格，
I like to use a thumb pick,
我喜欢用拇指拨片，
this is a Fred Kelly thumb pick,
这是 Fred Kelly 的拇指拨片，
nothing particularly special about it,
没有什么特别的，
there are other thumb picks as well to do it,
还有其他拇指拨片也可以这样做，
but in order to use this style,
但为了使用这种风格，
it's good to have a thumb pick,
有拇指拨片是很好的，
because you kind of need to angle it down a little bit different.
因为你需要稍微改变一下角度。
Okay, so let me just play a little bit for you using it,
好的，让我使用它为你们演奏一点，
and then I'll kind of describe what I'm doing, okay?
然后我会描述一下我做的，好的？
Now, that kind of a boom chick, a kind of a picking,
这是一种 boom chick ，一种拨动，
where you're hitting the bass notes and then the chord,
你击打低音音符，然后和弦，
[] did that a lot,
[]做了很多这样的事情，
it was all started with merle travis.
这一切都是从 Merle Travis 开始的。
What you need to do for this technique is
对于这个技巧，你需要做的是，
you have to kind of angle,
你必须以某种角度，
remember I told you how you should have your hand out,
记得我告诉过你，你应该手在外面，
well, forget that on this technique,
在这个技巧中，忘记那个，
you bring your hand, you put your palm,
你把你的手，你的手掌，
this part of your palm on the backside of your string,
手掌的这一部分放在你的弦的背面，
for the bass notes
对于低音音符，
and it kind of gets this muted sound,
它就会发出这种低音，
now it's just on the top few strings, the bass strings,
现在它只在最上面的几根弦上，低音弦，
while the ones down here, are still able to play the chord.
在这里的弦，仍然能够演奏和弦。
So it's a little bit tricky to get started,
所以开始有点棘手，
you have to angle your hand a little bit down,
你的手必须稍微向下倾斜，
I'm going to give you a simple exercise to get started with it,
我给你一个简单的练习来开始，
okay, we're just gonna try and get the notes first, okay.
好的，我们先试着得到音符，好的。
Here we go, exercise one in your book.
开始吧，书中的练习一。
Ready and go
准备，开始，
and you're looking for the correct sound you're playing,
你在寻找正确的演奏声音，
you want the note kind of choked off a little bit,
你想让音符有点卡住一点，
may take a little bit of practice to get that in the right spot,
可能需要一点练习才能把它放在正确的位置，
where it's giving you the right sound,
让它给你正确的声音，
now let's add a little bit of chords with it, okay,
现在让我们用它添加一点和弦，好的，
so it starts out on a C chord,
它从 C 和弦开始，
I'm going to do my bass notes,
我要做我的低音音符，
but I'm going to play the top of the C chord with these three fingers.
但我要用这三个手指演奏 C 和弦的高音。
Let's see if we can do this,
让我们看看是否能做到这一点，
I'll do it nice and slow,
我会做得很慢，
this is exercise 2,
这是练习 2 ，
ready go.
准备，开始。
Okay, now you slowly build more and more complex patterns on it,
好的，现在你慢慢地在上面建立越来越复杂的模式，
throw different chords into it,
在里面加入不同的和弦，
but that's basically what's going on there,
但基本上就是这样，
takes a little bit of sitting in your room going,
坐在你的房间里，
to actually get the flow of it,
真正地掌握它的流动。
once you do, it's a very rewarding style to play,
一旦你掌握了，这是一种非常有价值的演奏风格，
because you're kind of accompanying yourself,
因为你可以为自己伴奏，
you've got a baseline going,
你已经有了基线，
you've got the chords going,
你已经有了和弦，
you can also throw a melody on top,
你也可以在上面放一段旋律，
so it's a very interesting and fun technique to play,
所以它是非常有趣的演奏技巧，
so I encourage you to work on it.
所以我鼓励你在它上面努力。
Now you'll notice I'm switching between guitar,
现在你会注意到我在吉他之间切换，
some guitars lend themselves better to a steel string guitars,
一些吉他更适合于钢弦吉他，
lend themselves better to Merle Travis stuff
更适合 Merle Travis 的东西，
and some of the other fingerstyle techniques, that we've talked about
一些我们讨论的其他指弹技巧，
going to talk about classical guitar a little while,
更适合古典吉他，
I had to take classical guitar in college
我在大学有这个古典吉他，
and at first I thought gosh it's the biggest waste of time,
一开始我觉得这是最大的时间浪费，
it actually ended up being one of the most helpful skills that I now use as a player.
它实际上是我现在作为一名演奏家使用的最有用的技能之一。
So we're talking about hand position, that's the first thing,
所以我们谈论的是手的位置，这是第一件事，
again relaxed, put that hand forward a little bit, okay,
再次，放松一点，把那只手往前一点，
and you want to.
然后你想要。
Let me mention something a little bit about taking care of your nails,
让我提一下关于你的指甲的事，
on one hand, I don't have nails,
在一只手上，我没有指甲，
on my left hand, I don't have nails,
在我的左手上，我没有指甲，
on my right hand, although it's not huge nails,
在我的右手上，虽然不是很长的指甲，
I've got a little bit of nails on this hand,
我这只手有一点指甲，
it helps to give you the fingerstyle right [] sound,
它有助于给你指弹正确的声音，
if you get to grow your nails out just a little bit,
如果你把指甲稍微长一点，
you don't need to be really long,
你不需要非常长，
just a little bit is enough
只要一点点就足够了，
to get what you need to get, for a classical play.
得到你需要的古典演奏。
The emphasis is on a good balanced hand position,
重点是一个很好的平衡的手的位置。
each finger moving like a machine.
每个手指像机器一样移动，
Okay, one of the best studies,
好的，最好的学习之一，
you can get as far as studying classical stuff is
你可以学习古典的东西是
the right hand studies by Mario Giuliani,
Mario Giuliani 的右手研究，
any music store would be able to get it for you,
任何音乐商店都能为你买到它，
it's his classical right-hand studies
这是他的经典右手研究，
and all it does is takes you from a C chord to a G chord
它所做的就是把你从 C 和弦带到 G 和弦，
in about a 120 different ways,
用大约 120 种不同的方式，
every different combination of fingers that you can use,
你可以使用的每一种不同的手指组合，
we'll go through the first couple of them
我们将介绍前几种，
and that'll kind of get you started,
这将让你开始，
you'll kind of see what I'm talking about.
你会明白我在说什么。
Okay, so let's start with the number one, C chord,,
好的，让我们从第一个开始， C 和弦，
second one just arpeggios those chords that we just play,,
第二个是琶音我们刚刚演奏的那些和弦，
[] them and goes several different ways
[]它们，并通过几种不同的方式，
to give you different combinations of that,
为你提供不同的组合，
so if you're interested in classical guitar playing,
所以如果你对古典吉他演奏感兴趣，
it's a great skill for you to have in your tool kit for being able to play
它是在你的工具包中用于演奏的很好的技能，
and the Giuliani right hand studies are the best way to get started with that,
Giuliani 的右手研究是开始的最好的方法，
control is the main thing,
控制是主要的东西，
in our guitar tips section,
在我们的吉他 tips 部分，
we're gonna cover getting the control you need
我们将讨论你需要的控制，
to be a fantastic fingerstyle player,
成为一名出色的指弹的演奏者，
that I know you want to be
我知道你想成为这样的人，
and we're going to talk about building up speed,
我们将讨论如何提高速度，
so I'll see you there.
所以我们在那里见。
Okay, welcome to the guitar tips section,
好的，欢迎来到吉他 tips 部分，
there's a couple of things, four key things,
这里有四件关键的东西，
I think will help you be the fingerstyle player that you need to become
我认为会帮助你成为你需要成为的指弹演奏者，
and having done this for years and years and years.
而且已经做了很多年了。
These are four critical things,
这是四件关键的事情，
that you can do to improve your fingerstyle playing
你可以改进你的指弹演奏，
as you get started in it.
当你开始的时候。
Number 1, always practice with a metronome,
第一，总是用节拍器练习，
I've got my metronome handy right here,
我手边有我的节拍器，
as I'm doing these studies,
在我做这些学习的时候，
I started off at a tempo,
我开始一个节奏，
you're tempted as you're starting to play,
当你开始演奏时，开始一个节奏，
to get real woefully on the tempo,
为了真正掌握节奏，
a metronome forces you to play in the right tempo,,
节拍器迫使你以正确的节奏演奏。
then when I'm ready to go,
然后当我准备好时候，
I speed it up a little bit.
我会加速一点。
Now working with a metronome is never fun,
使用节拍器从来都不是一件有趣的事情，
it's not fun for me,
这对我来说并不有趣，
but I've got to do it
但我必须这样做，
and in almost every studio situation, I've been in,
在几乎我去过的每一个录音室环境，
almost all of them, you have some sort of a metronome going,
你有某种节拍器，
metronomes are what the pros use to get their tempos and and fingering steady,
节拍器是专业人士用来保持他们的节奏和手指稳定，
so I'd encourage you,
所以我会鼓励你，
it's frustrating you bet,
这很令人沮丧，
but it's the way to go,
但这是一种方法，
if you want to get speed and control of your finger,
如果你想获得速度和控制你的手指，
okay, you may be the one thinking that you don't need it,
好的，你可能是认为你不需要它的人，
but, I'll tell you from someone who's done it,
但是，我会告诉你，从一个有经验的人那里，
you're going to need a metronome.
你需要一个节拍器。
Number 2, for, in your fingering style technique,
第二个，在你的指弹技巧中，
number 2, slow down,
第二，放慢速度，
everybody always wants to go fast
每个人总是想要弹的很快，
and next thing you know they're tripping all over themselves,
然后他们被自己绊倒了，
they can't do it,
他们做不到，
their hand gets tense,
他们的手变得紧张，
they started slow tempo
他们开始慢节奏，
and next thing you know they want to go fast,
然后他们想要很快，
they want to be Mr hotshot
他们想成为高手先生，
and they don't learn the technique,
但他们不学习技术，
so my advice to you is slow down,
所以我给你的建议是慢下来，
how slow,
有多慢，
as stink and slow as you need to go
足够的慢，
to get your fingers doing what your brain is telling them to do,
让你的手指做你的大脑告诉他们做的事情，
yes, it's hard,
是的，这很难，
it takes a lot of thought
需要很多思考，
to get your fingers doing what they need to do,
让你的手指做它们需要做的事情，
but it's only when you do it slow,
但只有当你慢慢做的时候，
that you're actually training your hand,
你才是在训练你的手，
if you keep bumping your head up against the wall,
如果你一直用头撞墙，
trying to do it fast,
试图快速地做，
you can do that for years
你可以常年这样做，
and never get any better,
永远不会变得更好，
when actually doing slow few minutes each day is going to get you where you want to go.
而每天慢做几分钟就会把你带到你想去的地方。
Always practice with a metronome,
总是用节拍器练习，
slow down, number two.
慢下来，第二。
Number three use good technique,
第三，使用好的技巧，
that's one of the best things I learned,
这是我学到的最好的东西之一，
was getting a good right-hand technique,
那就是掌握一个好的右手技巧，
don't have your hand way far in the back,
不要把你的手放在后面太远，
bring that thumb forward a little bit,
拇指向前一点，
not too much, just a little bit,
不要太多，只是一点，
relax that wrist,
放松手腕，
as you speed up, don't tense up your hand,
当你加速的时候，手腕不要绷紧你的手，
that's going to be your hand tense,
你的手紧张，
you're gonna want to tense up that hand as you're getting faster and faster,
当你越来越快的时候，你会想要拉紧那只手，
relax that hand,
放松那只手，
your wrist needs to be slightly out,
你的手腕需要稍微出来，
you don't want to go flat with it like that,
你不会想这样把它平放，
not completely far out,
不是很远，
but just comfortable hand position.
只是手部姿势舒适。
Okay, the fourth and last thing is practice and repetition,
好的，第四件，也是最后一件事是练习和重复，
you don't get good fingerstyle technique by trying it once,
你不会试一次就得到好的指弹技巧，
it's a technique that is a physical thing
这是一种技术，一种体力的东西，
and it just takes sheer gun wrenching repetition,
它只需要简单的重复，
so sit there with a D chord and do these exercises,
所以坐在那里，用 D 和弦，做这些练习，
thumb 2 1 3, thumb 1 2 3, thumb 3 2 1,
拇指 2 1 3 ，拇指 1 2 3 ，拇指 3 2 1 ，
slow over and over and over again
慢一点，一遍又一遍地（练习），
until your mindI just melts out of your ears,
直到你的大脑从你的耳朵里融化，
and then you can start doing it with your fingers start doing
然后你可以开始用你的手指开始做，
without you having to think as much,
而你不必思考那么多，
so do it for a while, then come back to it, try it again,
所以做一段时间，然后回来，再试一次，
the whole idea is that you want to be able to start doing it fast without having to think about,
整个想法是你想要能够快速地开始做，而不必去想，
you maybe really lost in the thumb 1 2 3,
你可能会迷失在拇指 1 2 3 中，
do it over and over and over and over again,
一遍又一遍地重复，
the repetition will start to make that second nature,
重复将开始成为第二天性，
and it will start to going running on autopilot
它将开始自动运行，
to where you can start thinking about chords and making music.
在那里你可以开始思考和弦和创作音乐。
Okay, so here's your assignment for this time,
好的，这是你们这次的作业，
okay, practice practice the finger exercises that we have for you in your book,
好的，练习我们在书中为你们准备的手指练习，
extra exercises in there as well,
还有额外的练习，
for you to cover go over as many of them as you can,
尽可能多地覆盖，
I would encourage you to go through all of them,
我鼓励你通过所有的练习，
until you can play them at the right tempo that we have prescribed for you,
直到你能以我们为你规定的正确节奏演奏它们，
and smoothly and evenly,
节奏平稳地，
you can tell when you're kind of starting to get out of control,
当你开始失去控制的时候，你可以感觉到，
you want to be able to do it at the right tempo smoothly and evenly
你要以正确的节奏平稳地做这件事，
and last is practice the song Canon in D,
最后是练习音乐 D 大调卡农，
Pachelbel's Canon,
Pachelbel's 的 Canon ，
the very simple song,
很简单的一首歌，
I've made more money off of this song playing at weddings,
我在婚礼上演奏这首歌赚了很多钱，
so I can even remember I've played it so many times,
我甚至不记得我已经演奏多少次了，
it's a great song
这是一首很棒的歌，
and it's perfect for teaching arpeggios and fingerstyle technique,
它非常适合教授琶音和指弹技巧，
so we'll see at the workshop.
所以我们在 workshop 见。
Okay, welcome to the workshop time,
好的，欢迎来到 workshop 时间，
now here's where we get the good information
现在是我们获得好信息的地方，
that we've covered into our fingers and out into music,
我们已经掌握的手指和音乐，
we're going to start with reviewing the basic finger patterns,
我们将从回顾基本的手指模式开始，
what are the three basic finger patterns,
三个基本的手指模式是什么，
thumb 1 2 3, thumb 3 2 1 and thumb 2 1 3,
拇指 1 2 3 ，拇指 3 2 1 ，拇指 2 1 3 ，
we're going to start with the first one,
我们将从第一个开始，
in your finger exercises, we're going to be number one.
在你的手指练习中，是第一个。
We're just on open strings
我们处于空弦状态，
and we're gonna start out,
我们要开始了，
I'm gonna turn on my metronome here,
我要打开我的节拍器，
pretty slow tempo to start us out with.
开始的时候节奏很慢。
Ready, number one, go,
准备，第一个，开始，
go ahead and repeated,
继续，重复，
thumb out nice and front, relax that wrist,
拇指向外，手腕放松，
each finger firing,
每个手指拨动，
very good.
很好。
Okay, let's go to number two,
好的，让我们来看第二个，
I'll keep it right at that same tempo,
我会把它保持在相同的节奏上，
we're gonna work on that G chord first.
我们首先练习 G 和弦。
Ready, go,,
准备，开始，
go to a C chord,
换到 C 和弦，
D chord,
D 和弦，
stay right with that click,
保持与滴答声同步，
very good.
非常好。
Let's go on to number three,
让我们继续第三个，
okay, I'm gonna maybe click this up a little bit,
好的，我把这个往上调一点，
take it a little bit faster,
把它调快一点，
starts out on that G,
从 G 开始，
thumb 1 2 3,
拇指 1 2 3 ，
ready go,
准备，开始，
C chord,
C 和弦，
go back to that G chord, that's repeated,
回到 G 和弦，重复，
C chord.
C 和弦。
Great, let's go to number four,
很好，让我们去第四个，
let me crank it up a little bit more,
让我再把它调大一点，
starts at D chord,
从 D 和弦开始，
ready play,
准备，弹，
G chord,
G 和弦，
A chord,
A 和弦，
let's repeat it.
让我们来重复它。
Great, can I also to the second pattern,
很好，我们换到第二个模式，
which is thumb 3 2 1,
拇指 3 2 1 ，
I'll bring it back down slow for a second.
我会把它慢下来。
Let's do number one on the next page,
让我们做下一页的第一个，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
3 2 1, thumb 3 2 1, thumb 3 2 1,
3 2 1 ，拇指 3 2 1 ，拇指 3 2 1 ，
a whole idea is control,
整个想法是控制，
make your fingers do what your brain is telling them to do.
让你的手指做你的大脑告诉他们要做的。
Good, let's do number 2, speed it up a little bit,
好的，让我们做第二个，加快一点，
number two, two,
第二个，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
great.
很好。
Okay, now just for fun,
好的，现在只是为了好玩，
let's crank it up quite a bit,
让我们再把它调高一点，
going to number two again,
还是第二个，
a little bit faster,
快一点，
1 2, ready, go,
1 2 ，准备，开始，
great job.
做得很好。
Now, let's do number 3,
现在我们来做第三个，
we're on the third pattern now,
我们现在是第三个模式，
thumb 2 1 3,
拇指 2 1 3 ，
which for me is personally, the most that's the one I use the most.
对我个人来说是使用最多的。
Okay, let's try that,
让我们试一下，
starts on a G chord,
从 G 和弦开始，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
thumb 2 1 3, thumb 2 1,
拇指 2 1 3 ，拇指 2 1 ，
now C chord.
现在换到 C 和弦，
Okay, now let's do number four,
好的，现在我们来做第四个，
I've cranked up the tempo a little bit,
我把节奏调快了一点，
give us a little bit more practice on it,
让我们多练习一下，
let me bring it up a little bit more even
让我把它调得更快一点，
and let's do number four,
让我们做第四个，
1 2, ready go.
1 2 ，准备，开始，I
Okay, okay, let's bring it up just a little bit more,
好的，让我们再快一点，
try one more time,
再试一次，
ready go.
准备，开始，去，我们要看一看口袋铃铛，佳能d大调。
Good, okay, now we're Canon, Canon in D,
好的，现在看 Pachelbel's Cannon ， D 大调 Cannon ，
I'll try and get through as much of it as we can here,
我会尽我们所能地完成，
but you're probably going to do a good bit of work on your own.
但你们自己可能会做一些好的工作。
Okay, let's start,
好的，让我们开始，
it's mainly dealing with thumb 1 2 3,
主要是处理拇指 1 2 3 ，
our first fingering pattern,
我们的第一个指法模式，
starts on a D chord,
从 D 和弦开始，
goes through a lot of the open chords that we've already talked about,
经过了很多我们已经讨论过的开放式和弦，
as well as some of the barre chords,
以及一些封闭和弦，
so its a real good practice on all of this.
所以对这个是一个很好的练习。
Okay, let me, let me crank the tempo down, pretty far.
好的，让我把节奏调慢很多。
Here we go, let's try,
开始，让我们来试试，
1 2, ready, go.
1 2 准备，开始。
Okay, that's the first part of it,
好的，这是它的第一部分，
okay, let me speed it up a little bit more, just a little bit more
好的，让我再加快一点，
and we'll try it a little bit faster during that first part,
在第一部分，我们会试着更快，
now you also have a D with an f sharp in the base,
现在你还有一个基音是升 F 的 D ，
we haven't gotten to talking about those chords yet,
我们还没有讨论那些和弦，
but here's the form of it,
但这是它的形式，
it's basically a D chord
它基本上是 D 和弦，
and you have this f sharp with your second finger down there
你用你的中指按这个升 F ，
and that's what gets that F sharp there,
这就是升 F 的地方，
if you just follow the tablature,
如果你按照吉他谱，
I'll show you what to do,
我会告诉你怎么做，
here you go, first part again,
开始，第一部分，
ready, go,,
准备，开始，
slowly and evenly,
慢慢地，均匀地，
with an F sharp.
带着升 F 。
Good, and second part,
好的，第二部分，
just turn this off,
把这个关掉，
that second part,
第二部分，
I'll just play for you
我演奏一下，
and you can practice on your own.
你可以自己练习。
Okay, the second part,
好的，第二部分，
you're using thumb and third to get these first couple notes,,
你用拇指和无名指得到第一对音符，
it's always thumb and third,,
总是拇指和无名指，
that's part two.
这是第二部分。
And the third part here,
第三部分，
it gets into some sixteenth notes,
它变成了十六分音符，
so it's gonna take a little working on it
所以它需要一些工作，
to get these sixteenth notes down,
来完成十六分音符，
but it goes something like this,.
但它是这样的。
Great and the last part goes something like this.
很好，最后的部分是这样的。
Great, well I look forward to see you next time,
很好，我期待着下次再见，
you keep working on all the fingering and the fingerstyle things,
你继续练习所有的指法和指弹，
that we talked about a little practice will take you a long way,
我们谈到的一些练习会带你走很长一段路，
we'll see you later.
我们再见。